High God,
do you still remember
where I came from?
Qingqiu.
Exactly.
Qingqiu is the sacred land of my fox clan.
It is full of spiritual energy
and protected by my clan.
If you are willing to go there,
though you can only be reincarnated as a demon,
you can cultivate your magic earlier
to seek
what you are looking for.
Human or demon,
what does it matter?
As long as it's in the mortal world,
I don't care where my heart goes.
This is the sacred artifact of the Qingqiu fox clan,
the Soul-gathering Pearl.
With it,
you can definitely be reincarnated
as a member of the Qingqiu fox clan.
And it can quickly help you cultivate into human form
and walk in
the mortal world.
Thank you.
Hey, little girl.
Are you calling me?
What's your name?
I'm Yezi.
And you?
I'm Feilu.
How long have you been locked up?
About a month, I think.
How did you get caught?
I wasn't caught.
You weren't caught?
Then were you sent here?
There was a famine in our village.
The village chief sent me here
as a sacrifice to Lady Tu.
He hoped she would bless us with a good harvest next year.
Bah!
Isn't that total disregard for human life?
I've accepted my fate.
You've been locked up for a month.
Why haven't they eaten you?
They don't eat children.
There used to be many children here.
But they were all taken away
to be made into medicine.
I heard that to make the medicine,
they need to calculate an auspicious date and time.
I guess it's just not my turn yet.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely get you out of here.
You can't even save yourself.
How can you save me?
I...
My master is very powerful.
He will definitely come and save me.
Your master?
How could he be more powerful than Lady Tu?
In this world,
there is no one more powerful than my master.
Are you sure he will come?
He will definitely come.
Hyah!
We're here.
Let's go.
Here they come.
Prepare a welcome gift for our distinguished guests.
Yes, yes.
It seems
they really think highly of us.
We have to fight.
Divine Taiji,
manifestation of the universe,
thunder striking the purple skies,
heavenly might strike.
Zhen position.
Good.
As expected of a Golden Immortal.
You can still fight so well without your immortal body.
I'm impressed.
It's Master.
Master is here to save me.
If you encounter a monster,
shout at this,
'Sister, save me,'
and I will come.
Sister, save me.
Crazy.
Save me, sister.
It's Feilu.
It's an avatar I gave him before.
I've found his location.
Go save him.
Leave this to us.
Do you think I'm just for show?
Treating me as a mere decoration
wouldn't be very appropriate, would it?
What a pain.
Go.
It was a lie after all.
I'll just have to try.
I did it. I did it.
Wow.
Come with me.
Let's go.
Feilu.
Shh.
Wow.
Brother Feilu,
you are so amazing.
I'm still learning.
Yo,
you two kids,
where are you going?
Pingjieqianghaihui.
Pingjieqianghai.